{
    "subject": "Saeed_Akhtar_Mirza",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Mohan_Joshi_Hazir_Ho!",
    "human_readable": "Saeed Akhtar Mirza created Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7350468635559082,
            "question": "Who created the movie Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7240860462188721,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie created by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6550626754760742,
            "question": "Has Saeed Akhtar Mirza created any other notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6484211087226868,
            "question": "When was Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.574432909488678,
            "question": "Is Saeed Akhtar Mirza a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46113327145576477,
            "question": "What awards has Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4566654860973358,
            "question": "What is the plot of Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45187628269195557,
            "question": "Why is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! considered an important film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4346681237220764,
            "question": "What genre is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34615322947502136,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saeed Akhtar Mirza created Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14540_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14540_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! considered an important film?",
            "html": "yago_14540_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14540_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14540_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents list several films that Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed, including \"Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!\" from 1984. Therefore, the statement that Saeed Akhtar Mirza created Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Saeed Akhtar Mirza being the director of Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! was stated as a fact by Saeed himself speaking with The Indian Express, but it contradicts with his own description in the other contexts which state that he made notable parallel films such as Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! and others, implying that he created them, not directed.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}